http://www.linhoff.com/privacy/

Primary MenuUPLOAD + ORDERCreatePhoto GiftsCardsStationeryPhoto BooksCalendarsDécorCanvas PrintsMetal PrintsWood PrintsAcrylic PrintsFine Art PrintsFor BusinessPrintCreative PrintsLarge Format InkjetPosters + CollagesServicesArchiving + ScanningPrint ScansThe Gather BoxSlide + Negative ScansSpecialty ScanningRestorationVideo ServicesVideo TapesMovie FilmAudio MediaFilm DevelopingPassport PhotosPortrait StudioBusinessYour Creative PartnerBusiness DécorSignage + Display GraphicsBusiness PrintingONLINE PRINTINGLet’s TalkPhotographyBusiness HeadshotsOn Location PhotographySports + EventsSports + EventsHigh SchoolsTeam SportsDance StudiosSpecial Events Privacy PolicyYou are here: Home1 / Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyThe Print Refinery and Click Solutions, LLC. dba The Print Refinery – Edina are committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy Statement describes the information we collect from you, either online through this website, or social or mobile pages owned or operated by The Print Refinery, whether accessed via computer, mobile device or other technology, or offline via your purchase of The Print Refinery’s products, services, software, or other goods or interaction with The Print Refinery agents or employees (collectively Services), and how that information will be used. Please read this Privacy Policy Statement carefully, because by using the Services, you are acknowledging that you understand and agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and consent to the manner in which we may collect, use and disclose the following information. SECTION I. THE INFORMATION WE COLLECTWe and our service providers may collect information when you provide information to us and when information is collected automatically. Personal Information. You may choose to give us personally identifiable information online to allow us to communicate with you for marketing purposes, order notifications, and/or provide you with Services. Our online forms may ask for a small amount of relevant information, such as name, company name, email, street address, and phone number. Some forms may ask for a product serial number. If you make a purchase or order a repair, we may ask for your credit card number and billing information. Job applicants may be requested to provide information such as educational background, employment experience, and job interest. Usage Information. In addition to the information you may provide, we may collect information when you access or use the Services or a website “powered by” another company on behalf of The Print Refinery through our use of data collection technologies, including web beacons, cookies, and embedded web links. These technologies collect certain traffic information that your browser sends to a web site, such as your browser type and language, access times, and the address of the web site from which you arrived. They may also collect information about your Internet Protocol (IP) address. SECTION II. RIGHT FOR DATA CONSENT AND USAGEIn compliance with the General Data Protection Regulation enacted on May, 25, 2018, users are permitted the option to request and obtain confirmation that data is or is not being collected and for what purpose. They are also afforded the option to withdraw consent for use and purge their personal data from our records within a reasonable timeframe. To make this request, please email info@theprintrefinery.com  SECTION III. RECORDING OF COMMUNICATIONS WITH The Print RefineryIMPORTANT – PLEASE NOTE – All communications by and between The Print Refinery may be recorded or monitored for quality assurance, training and/or verification purposes. By engaging in any communication with The Print Refinery and its representatives, including without limitation, by submitting your contact information to The Print Refinery, requesting information regarding The Print Refinery’s products and/or engaging in telephone conversations with any of The Print Refinery’s representative, you are expressly consenting to the recording and monitoring of all such communications. In addition, you are acknowledging and agreeing to The Print Refinery’s Terms of Use and Privacy Policy as set forth on this website.NAVIGATECreateDécorPrintServicesSports + EventsBusinessQUICK LINKSOur StoryOur GuaranteeThe TeamCareersContactPR BlogCONTACT USQuestions? Comments? Contact Us or call us at 952.927.7333 HOURSMonday–Friday: 10am–6pm Saturday: 10am – 3pm Sunday: ClosedPassport Photos: Please call ahead to schedule!Now offering curbside drop-off + pick-up!  FROM THE BLOGWHY THIS YEAR’S HOLIDAY CARD IS SO SPECIALDecember 1, 2020 - 11:00 amFOUR SIMPLE STEPS TO PRESERVE YOUR FAMILY MEMORIES.May 1, 2020 - 2:31 pmJOIN OUR MAILING LIST
SUBSCRIBE!
You have Successfully Subscribed!
Scroll to top
